Jennifer Spriggs

Interaction Designer

Seattle, WA http://jenniferlspriggs.com

I build elegant visual solutions to complex creative problems. With over 8 years of experience designing and building products, I have a knack for quick iteration and problem solving with an eye for detail and form. I tackle problems holistically, designing with intention and empathy.

Recent Experience

Google (Adecco Vendor)

Interaction Designer Seattle, WA Nov. 2017 – Present

- aid in collecting quantitative and qualitative feedback to help drive concept direction and nascent product decisions
- build interactions and designs for the Clips camera and it's companion app
- collaborate closely with engineers to bring features from concept to implementation
- work to make AI and machine learning more approachable and human
- build prototypes with Framer, Sketch, Illustrator, HTML, CSS, etc.

Microsoft (KForce Vendor)

Product Designer II Seattle, WA Aug. 2017 - Nov. 2017

- built and presented wireframes and HD prototypes to executive partners
- refined interactions and nuance for Azure cloud pricing calculator
- worked with Sketch, Illustrator, and Framer.
- worked closely with the developers by building out design work flows and systems to minimize steps between prototype design and production code.

StratusCore

Lead Product Designer Seattle, WA Dec. 2017 – Aug. 2017

- developed SaaS platform and visualized dashboard for production companies and artists to manage their projects and production budgets
- created prototypes in Sketch and Adobe XD to support rapid testing and development
- responsible for all front-end code and development

Lulabop

UX Designer & Developer Seattle, WA Dec. 2016

- researched problems and solutions with current website architecture through user interviews and Google analytics synthesis
- prototyped and iterated deployable solutions with designer tools, then went straight to code in the Shopify platform
- deployed ahead of schedule to help client pitch and roll out new website, brand, and product to Home Depot for wholesale deal

LPK

Visual & Print Designer Cincinnati, OH Aug. 2015 – Sept. 2016

- created products for P&G's feminine care brands based on qualitative and quantitative user research
- inventor on several patents pending for the Always brand
- built collaborative design sessions to help P&G executives re-think feminine care and baby-care products

Education

General Assembly

UX Design Immersive | Seattle, WA | Sept. 2016 - Dec. 2016 Front & Back End Web Development | New York, NY | Sept. 2014 - Feb. 2015

Girl Develop It

Ruby 101 | Cincinnati, OH | Sept. 2016 - Dec. 2016

University of Cincinnati

Bachelor of Science in Fashion Design | Cincinnati, OH | 2007–2012

Skills	Development	Professional Groups
Adobe CC Sketch Invision Framer	HTML 5 CSS Javascript	StartupBus Rider AIGA Member Cincinnati Arts x Tech Board Member